相信爸妈看到我们送上的
I’m sure how mom and dad are surprised
结婚纪念日早餐一定会十分惊喜
by the anniversary breakfast we’re bringing to them.
我不想走进去看到他们两个光溜溜的
I hate to walk in if they are naked.
是啊  即便几年过去  每当夜不能寐
Yes, that kind of image could haunt someone
那画面总是在脑海中挥之不去
if she tries to sleep even years later.
放松点啦  你们安全了
Oh, relax. I think you are safe.
是吗
Or are they?
今天是我们结婚20周年纪念日
It’s our 20th anniversary,
所以在今天的学校园游会上
so today at the school fair,
一个名叫节奏老爹的乐队将以
a band called the Dad Beats
一首动感的浪漫民谣给克莱尔一个惊喜
is gonna surprise Claire with a power love ballad.
而乐队主唱  你最好坐下来
And the lead singer -- you might want to sit down --
就是独一无二的
is the one and only --
还是站起来吧  就是这个人
get up on your feet! -- this guy!
她貌美如天仙*
*She's a pretty sight
智慧比佛祖*
*Wise as a buddha
但是哥们  小心她咬你*
*But, brother, watch that bite
因为她是克莱尔小怪兽*
*’cause she's a Claire-acuda
要不还是别唱原创歌曲了
Or maybe an existing song.
谢谢
Thank you.
翻译：小饭  四方虾  冰蓝  罂粟无果  王大可  萌tu
时间轴：加森    校对：olivia_xuxu   后期&总监：瓜瓜
摩  登
家  庭
第五季 第七集
想不想在脸上画上
Do you want to get your face painted
美丽的蝴蝶
like a pretty butterfly?
不想  我没那心情
No. I'm just not in the mood.
莉莉  你呢
Lily, what about you?
知道吗
You know what?
我可以让他们画
Maybe I will have them paint
"史上最差教练"几个字在我额头上
"Worst coach ever" on my forehead.
小卡最近在教新生打橄榄球
Cam's coaching freshman football,
但他的球队总是输
and his team's losing,
这让他有点紧张焦虑
and it's making him, uh, a little tense.
快跑  快跑
Run, run!
像保护你的孩子一样护着球
Protect it like it's your baby!
你把你的孩子弄丢了
You dropped your baby!
你丢了你的孩子
他们抱着你的孩子跑了
They're running away with your baby!
快去抢你的孩子
Go get your baby!
这裁判比选罗素・高尔
That's the worst call since
出演《悲惨世界》的人还差劲
they cast Russell Crowe in "Les Mis,"
就在那啊
right there!
你看到大家是怎么瞪我的吗
You see the way everyone's glaring at me?
-没有  -好像我是个窝囊教练
- No. - Like a big loser coach.
都是你自己瞎想罢了
All in your head.
我就是新生橄榄球队的海丝特・白兰
I'm the Hester Prynne of freshman football.
我不如在衬衫上绣一个
I may as well have a
猩红色的"L"好了[Loser: 废物]
scarlet "L" sewn on my shirt.
那大家会以为你是拉芙妮
Well, then, everyone would think you're Laverne.
[ABC台情景喜剧《拉芙妮与雪莉》中的人物]
塔克教练
Coach Tucker.
昨晚输得很惨啊
That was a tough loss last night.
是啊  确实很惨
Yeah, yeah. Sure was.
我知道你很失望  肯定的
I feel your frustration. Sure do.
米奇尔  这是特雷弗的爸爸约翰
Uh, Mitchell, this is John. He's Trevor's dad.
-抱歉  -明星跑卫
- Sorry. - Star running back.
恐怕打不了多久了
Well, maybe not for long.
我正在考虑让他退队
I'm seriously thinking about pulling him from the team.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
因为特雷弗总是被拦截抢球
'cause trevor's getting killed out there.
你没安排人为他阻截对手
You got no one to block for him.
我明白你的意思了  你说得没错
I-I hear what you're saying, and you're not wrong,
但给我一点时间
but give me a little time.
给你一星期
You got one week.
在园游会上这样太不合适了
Well, that is not appropriate fair behavior at all.
你知道什么能让你开心点吗
You know what might make you feel better?
召集球队  让队员心中充满对神的敬畏
Gathering my team and putting the fear of God in them.
我本来要说的是西班牙油条
I was gonna say a churro.
我可以两个一起来
I can do both!
她真是一团糟
She's a mess.
丫头
Girl...
快车手  转弯时悠着点
Hey, hey, lead foot, easy on the turns!
这蛋糕我做了好几个小时呢
I worked hours on this cake.
你确定要去吗
You're sure you want to do this?
我要拿下蛋糕比赛
I'm going to win the cake contest,
这样再也没什么能阻止我了
and then there'll be no stopping me.
阻止你什么  被揍一顿吗
From what? A beating?
冠军绶带会赢得尊重的  杰
First-place ribbons earn respect, Jay.
但如果跟你竞争的是一群
Not if your competition's
老女人和怪胎就没这效果了
a bunch of old ladies and weirdos.
你就不能友善一点吗
Could you just be nice?
你吃他练习做的那些蛋糕时
You didn't seem to care
好像一点也不在乎啊
when you were eating all his practice cake.
总算有车位了
Finally.
你打算怎么办啊  伙计
What are you gonna do, pal?!
我也正想问你呢
About to ask you the same thing.
你没看到我的指示灯吗
Did you not see my blinker?
-没  -那你就是瞎了  灯还在闪呢
- Nope. - Then you're blind, 'cause it's on.
看你这样  我估计一整路都闪着呢吧
Looking at you, I'm guessing it was on the whole way here.
我车上有卫星广播  我能跟你耗一整天
I got all day and satellite radio.
我才不管把车停在这里是不是你的遗愿
I don't care if parking here is on your bucket list.
我有两本有声书  一条太空毯
I've got two books on tape, a space blanket,
手套箱里还有一整根能量棒
and a protein bar in the glove box.
有必要的话  我就睡在这里
I will sleep here if I have to.
我们坚决不动
We're not moving.
随便你  但我俩要走了
Ay, but we are.
走吧  曼尼
Let's go, Manny.
-你是谁  -老天啊
- Who are you? - Oh, my god!
你把我吓尿了
You scared the hell out of me!
注意用语哦  家里有个小宝宝呢
Okay, language. There's a baby in the house.
那宝宝是我舅舅
Uh, that baby happens to be my uncle.
那你是哪个
Which one are you?
你得告诉普先生你打碎了他的一瓶啤酒
You need to tell Mr. P you broke one of his beers.
我是艾丽克斯  你是谁
I'm Alex. Who are you?
我是他们的男保姆[曼尼]
I’m their Manny.
得了吧
Nice try.
我认识他家的曼尼  你和他一点也不像
I know their Manny, and you look nothing like him.
你是海莉
Oh, you're Haley.
我是他家的男保姆  安迪
I'm their male nanny, Andy.
你真的得挪个位了
You really need to move.
好吧  我去泳池边了
Okay, well, I'll be out by the pool.
什么  不行
What? Nope!
不行
No, no, no.
没允许的话就不行
Not without permission, you're not.
-我要给普先生和太太打电话  -等等
- I'm gonna call Mr. and Mrs. P. - Oh, wait!
说真的  曼迪  你...
Um...seriously, Mandy, do you, uh --
你真的非得那样做吗
do you really have to do that?
我知道你在耍什么把戏
I see what you're doing.
别费心了
Don't bother,
我在犹他有个
because I have a girlfriend
交往了八年的女友[八岁的女友]
of eight years back in Utah.
她真幼齿  但我想那边的作风
That's pretty young, but I guess they do things
也许不同吧
differently over there.
她和我一般年纪
She's my age,
我们订婚了  就要订婚了
and we're engaged... to be engaged.
这叫提前订婚
It's -- it's a pre-engagement.
她是海岸警卫队的
She's in the coast guard.
-在犹他州吗  -是啊
- In Utah? - Yeah.
那里有西半球最大的咸水湖
It's the largest salt lake in the western hemisphere.
很不错  她在保护我们的湖哎
Oh, good. She's protecting our lake.
我去泳池边啦
I'll be out by the pool.
你老板在召唤你
Your boss is calling you.
这位美女在这里啊
Hey! There she is.
我不会给你钱的
Yeah, I'm not giving you any money.
我不要你的钱  我需要的是建议
I don't need your money -- I need advice...
关于一个女孩的
about a girl.
真恶心  但我很感兴趣  说吧
Gross, but I'm intrigued, so talk.
艾丽克斯  闺蜜
Alex. Hey, Girlita.
西恩娜  闺蜜
Sienna...girl!
西恩娜太棒了  她时髦  善于处世
Sienna is amazing -- stylish, worldly --
她刚刚来我们学校  还没意识到
and she's so new to our school, she doesn't even realize
我比她低一个社会阶级
that I'm a full social class below her.
我需要在她发现学校有自助餐厅前
I need to cement the friendship
巩固我们的友谊
before she finds out we have a cafeteria.
我到处在找你
I've been looking all over for you.
这是我弟弟  卢克
Uh, this is my little brother, Luke.
他想要一些建议  因为他迷上了个女孩
He wants advice on some lame crush he has.
这可是大事啊
That's huge.
超级重大
So huge.
卢克  这个神秘的女孩是谁
So, Luke, who is this mystery woman?
就是一个普通的女生啦
Um...just some girl.
她的名字是西恩娜
And her name is Sienna.
曼尼  我只说最后一遍
You know, Manny, I'm just gonna say this one last time.
-我深表怀疑  -给我
- I doubt that. - Give me that.
你想更合群吗
You want to fit in?
靠这个蛋糕比赛
You're not doing yourself any favors
可帮不了你什么忙
with this cake contest.
不一定  厨师很能吸引女性
I don't know. Chefs get all the girls.
你就是个烤蛋糕的
You're a baker.
烤蛋糕的都是女的
Bakers are girls --
贝蒂・克罗克  菲尔斯太太  小黛比
Betty Crocker, Mrs. Fields, Little Debbie.
[都是蛋糕店品牌]
那面团宝宝呢
What about the Pillsbury Doughboy?
回得好  曼尼
That's a good one, Manny!
瞧瞧是谁  杰・普里契特
Well, well, well. Jay Pritchett.
你总算来了啊
Nice of you to finally show up.
-什么情况  -你是官方公正警察
- What's happening? - You're an official fair cop.
-你妻子给你报了名  -歌洛莉亚
- Your wife volunteered you. - Gloria!
我爱你  玩得开心哦
I love you! Have fun!
-这是什么玩意  -这是为了慈善事业
- What is this? - It's for charity.
人们付钱给你  让你去
People pay for you to arrest
把坏人抓进监狱蹲10分钟
and throw somebody in jail for 10 minutes.
这是你的搭档
And here comes your partner.
你好啊
What's up?
该死  我可不要和这个小丑合作
Oh, hell, no. I'm not working with this clown.
你叫谁小丑呢  遗愿清单
Hey, who are you calling a clown, bucket list?
看来你俩已经见过面了
I see you two have already met.
是我先把车开进车位的  你心里清楚
That was my space and you know it.
跟我的车去说吧  你知道上哪去找
Tell it to my car. You know where to find it.
够了  你俩别吵了
Hey, enough of you two squabbling.
家庭教师协会盯着我呢
I've got the PTA breathing down my neck.
把这个别上  然后开始工作
Just pin these on and get to work.
不行  我不能别警徽  抱歉
Nope. Can't do the badge. Sorry.
我妻子刚给我买了这件衬衫
My wife just bought me this shirt,
如果我弄坏了它  她会杀了我的
and if I ruin it, she'll kill me.
你害怕自己会弄坏你的女式衬衫啊
You're afraid you'll ruin your blouse.
这不是女式衬衫  而是衬衫
It's not a blouse! It's a shirt.
她在男装部买的  所以是衬衫
She bought it at the men's department, so it's a shirt.
这是你们第一个要逮捕的人
Here's your first arrest.
她在头晕龙游戏区
She's over at the Dizzy Dragon.
提示一下  听说她比看上去更强硬
Word on the midway is she's tougher than she looks.
-你们能应付吗  -我为什么不能应付
- Think you can handle it? - Why couldn't I handle it?
因为她是你女儿
'Cause she's your daughter.
喂
Hello?
常先生  你好
Oh, hi, Mr. Chang. Yeah.
你说你已经到我家了是什么意思
What do you mean you're at the house already?
你们应该两小时后才过去的啊
You're not supposed to be there for another two hours.
过去我一直送给菲尔
I have a long history of giving Phil
糟糕的结婚纪念礼物
bad anniversary gifts,
但今年  我计划了超棒的礼物
but this year, I have planned something amazing.
传统的结婚20周年纪念礼物是瓷器
The traditional 20th gift is china,
但我要怎么办  难道送他一个盘子吗
but what am I gonna do, give him a plate?
我已经送过了
I already did that.
[人猿星球]
好  拜拜
Okay, bye.
亲爱的  我们收拾收拾回家吧
Honey, um, what do you say we pack it in and go home?
什么  不行  我们才刚到
What? No. I mean, we just got here.
我还没玩敲鼹鼠游戏呢
I haven't even whacked a mole yet.
我知道  但我刚从摩天轮上下来
I know, but I just got off the Ferris wheel,
我现在觉得特别恶心
and I'm feeling really queasy.
但你要错过节奏老爹乐队表演了
But you're gonna miss the Dad Beats.
那可不行  来吧
No way. Come on.
去给你买个炸酸黄瓜
Let's get you a fried pickle!
菲尔  我会吐出来的
Phil, I might throw up.
我没开唱前谁都不会吐
No one throws up until I sing.
菲尔  我们得走了  现在就回家
Phil, we got to go. We got to go home now.
行  好吧  又没什么把你困在这里
Sure. Why not? Nothing keeping you here.
你怎么行为这么怪异
Why are you acting weird?
我没行为怪异啊
I'm not acting weird.
抓住她了
Got her.
女士  你被捕了
Ma'am, I am afraid you are under arrest.
不  爸  告诉他我现在没空玩这游戏
Uh, no. Dad, tell him I can't do this right now.
别这样  拜托了
Come on. Please.
来吧  读读她的罪状
Go ahead. Read her the charges.
我读不出口
Can't do this.
好吧  我们来看看
All right. Let's see.
你被控告非法性感
You have been charged with unlawful sexiness
及屁屁火辣
and possession of a hot booty.
这太恶心了
That is wrong.
-罪名成立  -别闹了
- Guilty as charged. - Stop it!
行了  去监狱里蹲10分钟
All right, 10 minutes in the slammer.
不行  我不能
No, I can't.
我没时间玩游戏  菲尔
I don't have time for this. Phil!
我的天
Oh, my god!
你干什么呢  变态
What are you doing, perv?!
为消失的两瓶啤酒留下罪证
Getting proof of where the two missing beers went.
你不能在这外边喝酒
You can't drink that out here.
我们来看看你说得对不对
Hmm. Let's see if you're right.
不对
Mm, no.
好吧  你在泳池区
Okay, well, you're in a pool zone,
啤酒瓶是玻璃做的  这不安全
and that is glass, so that's not safe.
很危险
It's dangerous.
你和你女朋友怎么都这么热衷保护水源
What is with you and your girlfriend protecting water?
好吧
Okay, just --
你给我...不  不
If you just -- no -- no, uh, uh!
该...该死
Oh! D-- ahh! D-d-- oh, dilly!
这可是你干的
Well, now you've done it.
你得爬进去把泳池里
You're gonna have to climb in there
所有的玻璃渣找出来
and get all the glass out of the pool.
我刚把头发拉直
Um, I just got my hair straightened,
所以我是不可能下水的
so that's not gonna happen.
我讨厌发脾气
I hate to go all ballistic,
但认识你真不是件愉快的事
but it has not been a pleasure meeting you.
你用那张嘴亲你的假想女友吗
Do you kiss your imaginary girlfriend with that mouth?
对  但她真实存在  她是个真姑娘
I do, but she's real. So, she's a real girl.
这一切都归结于一件事  先生们
It all comes down to one thing, gentlemen --
专注
focus...
还有团队合作和用心
and teamwork and heart!
你们看到这根木锤了吗
You see this mallet?
你们觉得我能用一根手指转动这根木锤吗
Think I can swing this here mallet with one finger?
不能  我需要整个团队
No! I need my whole team!
因为当你们作为一个团队行动和工作时
Because when you're functioning and working as a team,
先生们  看好了
gentlemen, look out!
狂野老太婆
Sassy granny?
是的  狂野老太婆
Yeah, sassy granny.
是的  完全正确
Yes, exactly.
因为这就是你们昨晚在赛场上的表现
Because that is what you all played like last night --
一群狂野老太婆
is a bunch of sassy grannies.
但是这个星期我们要竭尽全力
But we're gonna bust our humps this week,
我们要冲上赛场
and we're gonna get out there,
打起比赛来要像一群...
and we're gonna play like a bunch of...
娘娘腔  明白了
Girly men. Got it.
好吧  那什么  这东西插上电源了吗
Okay, you know what? Is this thing plugged in?
这机器不需要电源
It's not electric.
好像是19世纪制造的
I think it was made in the 1800s.
好的  这就是我要说的
Okay, well, that's my point.
这机器过时了
This is outdated.
而且很无礼
This is offensive,
因为姑娘们也可以是运动员
because girls are athletes, too.
所以  结论就是
So, in conclusion...
如果你想赢得一场橄榄球赛
if you want to win football games,
就得走上赛场  打比赛要像...
we got to go out there and play like a...
大爸在干吗
What is daddy doing?
大爸在痛击他的恶魔
Daddy's smashing his demons.
就像你在家用吸尘器吸除的那些东西吗
Oh, like the ones you vacuum up at home?
对  对  就是那样
Yeah, yeah. Like that.
该死  就差一点儿
Mm! Damn. Near miss.
你为什么为了个校园活动盛装打扮
Why the hell are you so dressed up for a school fair, anyway?
这怎么叫盛装打扮
How is this dressed up?!
我...为什么这么说
I'm -- why?
因为我的衬衫有扣子吗
Because my shirt has buttons?
这是什么面料  是丝绸吗
What's that fabric? Is that silk?
别用你那沾满冰激凌的手指碰我的衬衫
Get your vanilla fingers away from my shirt!
-女士衬衫  -好吧
- Blouse. - Okay...
你想谈衣服是吗  那我们就谈谈衣服
You want to talk about clothes? Let's talk about clothes.
谈吧  来看看
Let's go. Let's see.
你穿得像个年老过气的高尔夫球手
You look like some kind of old, washed-up golf pro
一路比赛一路买醉
who drank his way off the tour
就差拿支小铅笔
and is one step away from writing a suicide note
写自杀遗书了
with one of them little pencils.
对不起  我不是那个意思
Sorry. I didn't mean that.
你要不是那个意思就不会那么说了
You wouldn't have said it if you didn't mean it.
我没有穿时髦衣服的身材
I don't have the body to wear the clothes they make today,
所以我挑舒服的穿
so I dress comfortable.
你身材很好啊  伙计
You're in shape, man.
你有多大  50多吗
What are you? Late 50s?
别开玩笑了  明显不是
Come on. You know I'm not.
我说真的  伙计
I'm serious, man.
你看起来像常驻健身房的
Y-you look like you live at the gym.
-我偶尔散步  -是吧
- I do some walking. - Yeah?
普里契特  威廉姆斯
Pritchett, Williams,
摩天轮那里有个人需要拘捕
got another arrest over by the Ferris wheel.
收到
On it.
我们走
Here we go.
为什么要把冰激凌扔了
Why'd we throw out the ice cream?
我们有的是时间
We got plenty of time.
看着曼尼在那
Seeing Manny up there
跟那些怪人和他们的怪蛋糕在一起
with the misfits and their crazy cakes,
我开始怀疑杰可能是对的
I started to wonder if Jay was right.
要是曼尼更像其他男孩那样
Maybe Manny would fit in better
也许他能更合群
if he was more like the other boys.
也许我需要帮他一把
And maybe I needed to give him a little push.
我全看见了
I saw you.
县监狱
好了  小姑娘
All right, young lady.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
-什么  -你有权保持沉默
- What? - You have the right to remain silent.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
爷爷
Grandpa!
抱歉  孙女  职责所在
Sorry, honey. Part of the job.
让开点
Out of the way!
我们走吧
Let's go.
这是谁干的
Who did this?!
看来只剩我们两个了
Hmm. I guess it's just you and me.
我的蛋糕  有人把它毁了
My cake! Somebody ruined it!
谁会这么干
Who would do that?!
曼尼  太可怕了  你的心血啊
Ay! Manny, how terrible. All your hard work.
算了  那我们去玩吧
Oh, well. Let's go ride the rides.
不不  妈妈  我知道是谁干的
No, no, no. Mom, I know who did it.
真的吗
Oh, you do?
是伊妮德
It was Enid.
看看她
Ah. Look at her.
你能看到她眼中的愤恨
You can see the hate in her eyes.
她一看到我的蛋糕  就感到了威胁
The minute she saw this, she felt threatened.
这个冷血贱人
She's cold as ice.
何不随它去呢
How about you just let it go
去和其他男孩们玩玩吧
and go play with the other boys?
那正合她意
Oh, she'd love that.
好啊  伊妮德
Okay, Enid.
你想玩玩吗  那我们就来玩玩
You want to dance? Let's dance.
把手机给我  拜托  我要打个电话
Let me have my cellphone. Come on. I got to make a call.
抱歉  规定不允许
Sorry. Those are the rules.
你笑什么
What are you smiling at?
我6岁
I'm six.
天呐
Oh, god.
好了  又给你们送来一个
All right. Got another one for you here.
亲爱的
Hi, honey.
进去吧
Come on.
罪状是这个大姐太凶残
One count of being an aggravating big sister.
关8到10分钟
That's 8 to 10 minutes.
是卢克干的吗  我是在帮他啊
Luke did this?! I was just trying to help him.
帮他干什么
Help him do what?
我朋友西恩娜和我正帮他
My friend Sienna and I were trying to help him
找到他喜欢的那个女孩
find this girl he has a crush on.
宝贝  西恩娜就是他喜欢的女孩
Honey, Sienna is the girl he has a crush on.
拜托  你没看到他看她的眼神吗
Come on, haven't you ever seen the way he looks at her?
像他以前看万圣节糖果的眼神一样
It's same way he used to look at Halloween candy.
天呐  他要做蠢事了
Oh, my god. He's gonna do something stupid
他会毁了我的好事
and ruin it for me.
我得出去
I have to get out of here.
好吧  我有个主意  听我的
Okay. All right. I got a plan. I got this.
我来调虎离山
I'm gonna create a distraction.
把那个小警卫引到这来
Just got to get that little guard over here.
你就安静地坐着
You're gonna sit down very quietly,
坐在门边
right by the door.
好主意  妈妈  记得告诉我结果如何
Great plan, mom. Let me know how that works out for you.
那是个假锁
It's a fake lock.
你要在那坐多久
How long were you gonna sit on that?
又找到一块
Found another one.
我就说吧
I told you.
你每次都要这样炫耀吗
Are you gonna do that every time?
你找到的是玻璃渣
You found glass,
又不是消失的亚特兰大城
not the lost city of Atlanta.
估计那个城就是因为有太多
Wow, I'm gonna chalk that one up
未成年人饮酒才沉没的
to a lot of underage drinking.
-你流血了  -什么
- You're bleeding. - What?
我晕血  我晕血
I do not like blood. I do not like blood.
-严重吗  -我看看
- Is it bad? - Here.
-天呐  -怎么了
- Oh, my god! - What?
你的手指又短又粗  像小胡萝卜
Your fingers are so stubby,  like baby carrots.
好吧
Sure. Okay.
嘲笑我吧
Make fun...
总有一天你会需要我把手伸进贩卖机里
till you need me to reach into a vending machine,
到时候大家都要巴结我了
then I'm everyone's best friend.
来  举着别动
Here. Hold still.
我来压住止血
Let me put some pressure on it.
你为什么要当男保姆呢
So, why are you a manny, anyway?
赚钱上大学
Saving up for college.
而且我喜欢孩子
Plus, I like kids.
因为和他们一起你的手显得正常吗
'Cause they make your hands seem normal?
好了  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
我没事了  谢谢
I'm good. Thank you.
卢克  我不想打击你
Luke, I hate to say it,
但也许那女孩已经离开了
but maybe this girl left.
这也许是最好的结果
It's probably for the best.
我是说  即便我找到她
I mean, even if I found her --
算了  当我没说  这很难为情
ah, forget it. It's embarrassing.
没事  说吧
No. Tell me.
我不知道该做些什么
I wouldn't know what to do.
我从来没有亲过女孩子
I've never kissed a girl before.
其实没有那么难
Oh! It's not that hard.
不如这样吧
You know what?
我亲你一下给你看看是什么感觉
I'll kiss you once to show you how it's done.
真的么  好  那我们去垃圾桶后面吧
Really? Okay. Want to go behind the dumpster?
不用  在这里就可以
No. Here is fine.
好吧  虽然跟我原来想象的不一样
Okay. It's not really how I imagined it, but...
停下
Stop!
什么  别理她  我们到哪一步了
What? Ignore her. Where were we?
你就是那个女生  他喜欢你
You're the girl! You're his crush!
他是个小怪胎  请别因此对我另眼相看
He's being a little weirdo! Please don't judge me!
卢克  这是真的么
Uh, Luke, is this true?
她是个书呆子  她的朋友都是书
She's a nerd! Her friends are books!
你是发生在她身上最好的事
You're the best thing that's ever happened to her!
-艾丽克斯  -我不知道他在说什么
- Alex? - Um, I don't know what he's talking about!
好吧  我要去找我的朋友们了
Okay, I'm just gonna go catch up with some friends.
西恩娜  等等
Sienna, wait!
别伤心  反正她也配不上你
Don't be sad. You're too good for her anyways.
是啊  谢谢  艾丽克斯
Yeah. Thanks, Alex.
没说你
Not you.
我在说我自己  你这个小矮人
I was talking about myself, you little gnome.
他在那
There he is.
再逮捕一个人  我们就能收工了
One more arrest and we can hang up our badges.
我之前就看到这个小混混到处捣乱
I've seen this punk horsing around earlier.
我会享受这一刻的
I'm gonna enjoy this.
该坐牢了  穿牛仔夹克的那个
Jail time, jean jacket.
-是不是很糟  -你会没事的
- Is it bad? - You're gonna be fine.
我应该穿个马甲的
Aah! I should have worn a vest.
为什么每个人都站在那里看着
Why is everyone just standing around?!
拿条毛巾来给他擦衬衫啊
Get this man a towel for his blouse!
好冷
So cold.
我们差点就成功了
We were almost out.
-我不想就这样结束  -你不许那样做
- I didn't want it to end like this. - Don't you do that!
事情还没结束
It's not over!
听我说
Listen to me.
我需要你告诉我太太事情的经过
I need you to tell my wife what happened.
告诉她这不是我的错
Tell her it wasn't my fault.
你可以自己跟她说
You're gonna tell her yourself.
她就站在那里  看起来很生气
She's standing right there, and she looks pissed.
宝贝
Hi, baby.
菲尔
Phil...
菲尔  我说了我们得回家了  说真的
Phil, when I said we needed to go home, I meant it.
对不起  我应该听你的话
I'm sorry. I should have listened to you.
但你一定要留下来再听一首歌
But you have to stay for just one song.
为什么
Why?
相信我
Trust me.
大家好么
Whoo! How's everybody doing?!
好
Good!
好的  下一位  我们有请
All right, next up, we have
一位非常特别的来宾
a very special guest joining us.
女士们先生们  请将掌声献给
Ladies and gentlemen, give it up for...
-哈罗德・格罗斯曼  -等等
- Harold Grossman! - Wait.
什么
What?
我以前从没做过类似的事情
Uh, never really done anything like this before.
药房的一些朋友
Uh, some of the gang down at the pharmacy
劝我来的
talked me into it, so...
必须花些时间*
*Gotta take a little time
花些时间去思考*
*A little time to think things over
读懂其中隐含的意义*
*I'd better read between the lines
以便日后不时之需*
*In case I need it when I'm older
在我的人生中*
*In my life
没想到我们的药剂师哈罗德・格罗斯曼
Turns out Harold Grossman, our pharmacist,
是个摇滚明星
is a rock star.
他的歌声简直可以作为良药出售
His voice is the drug he should be dispensing,
因为很显然  那能治愈一切
because apparently, it's the cure for everything.
-该走了  我们走吧  -别别别
- Time to go. Let's go. - No, no, no, no, no!
等等  等等  拜托  他好棒
Stay, stay, stay, stay! Come on, he's great! Whoo!
我想让你告诉我*
*I want you to show me
我想感受到什么是爱*
*I want to feel what love is
而我知道  我知道*
*And I know, and I know
我知道你可以告诉我*
*I know you can show me
他太棒了
Oh, he's incredible!
-是啊  -太棒了
- I know. - Incredible!
哈罗德・格罗斯  各位
Harold Grossman, everybody!
我的天哪
Holy cow!
谁能想到呢
Who knew?!
让我们将热情持续下去
Let's keep this party going.
接下来  我们今天还有一位来宾
Next up, we have one more guest today.
不
Oh, no.
哈罗德
Harold, yeah.
哈罗德  哈罗德
Harold, Harold!
好吧  好吧
Okay, now. Okay.
也许哈罗德稍后可以再返场
Maybe Harold can come back a little later.
但此时此刻
But in the meantime,
节奏老爹乐队很荣幸地为您呈上
the Dad Beats are proud to present...
菲尔・邓菲
Phil Dunphy!
谁
Paul who?
菲尔
Phil?
菲尔・邓菲
Phil dunphy.
-是我啊  -天呐
- Oh, Phil Dunphy. - Oh, boy.
停车场有一辆白色面包车
There's a white minivan out in the parking lot
车灯没关  车牌号TCB-R2D2
with its lights on -- license plate number TCB-R2D2.
掌声送给菲尔・邓菲  大家
Phil Dunphy, everybody.
妈  看这个
Hey, mom. Check it out.
-我的蛋糕弄好了  -真不错啊
- I finished my cake. - Oh, good.
这是11.5级地震之后的洛杉矶
It's Los Angeles after an 11.5 earthquake.
我叫它"地糕"
I call it earth-cake.
曼尼  真赞
Manny, that's amazing!
你觉得这很赞
You think that's amazing?
等会看我把这玩意儿
Wait till I smash this thing
砸在伊妮德的单层蛋糕上
right on top of Enid's piece of sheet cake.
别别别  等等  不是伊妮德干的
No, no, no! Wait! Manny, Enid didn't do it.
-是我干的  -什么
- I did it. - What?
是我毁了你的蛋糕
I was the one who ruined the cake.
我怕那些男孩子嘲笑你
I was afraid that all those boys were gonna make fun of you.
我觉得我比你更在乎你是否合群
I think I care more about you fitting in than you do.
不  我在乎
No. I care.
我非常在乎
I care a lot.
只是我擅长的事情
It's just the stuff I'm good at
不会让我受欢迎
isn't the stuff that makes you popular.
请各位选手在60秒内
Contestants, all cakes
将蛋糕放在评委桌前
must be at the judges' table in 60 seconds.
这么多人  我们怎么可能挤得过去
Ay, there's no way we're gonna make it through that crowd.
不可能挤不过去  拿着
Like heck we won't. Here.
-什么  -跟着我
- What? - Follow my lead.
-好的  -准备好了吗  来
- Okay. - Ready? Come on.
看看谁终于放下他的木锤了
Oh, well, look who finally put down his mallet.
你发完脾气了吗
You done having your little temper tantrum?
没有那么糟啦
It wasn't that bad.
小卡  你的行为也太幼稚了
Cam, your behavior was completely juvenile,
我不觉得这会给莉莉
and I don't think that it set a very good example --
别插队
Hey, hey! No cutsies --
树立好榜样
for Lily.
对不起  我太沮丧了
I'm sorry. I'm just frustrated.
我感觉无法让球队反败为胜了
I-I can't seem to turn this team into a winner.
你为什么要给自己这么大压力呢
Oh, why do you let it get you so stressed out?
不就是橄榄球吗
It's just football.
你知道橄榄球对我来说意味着什么吗
You know what football was to me?
橄榄球是我的救赎
Football was my salvation.
每当我踏上赛场
Every time I stepped onto that field,
我就不再是那个被孤立的怪咖基佬了
I wasn't the weird gay outsider kid anymore.
我是球队的榜样
I inspired my entire team
因为我有想要证明的东西
because I had something to prove.
我的那个想要证明自己的小孩去哪了
Where's my kid that has something to prove?
妈  快点儿
Come on mom!
快跟上我  跟紧点儿
Stay on my hip! Follow my lead!
快
Move!
这正是我需要的
That's exactly what I need.
快点  快点  妈
Oh! Come on! Come on, mom.
需要蛋糕吗
Cake?
告诉他们你的好消息
Tell them the good news.
-我赢了蛋糕比赛  -另外一个好消息
- I won the cake contest! - The other good news.
他加入了球队
He made the football team.
他们第一次赢了比赛
They won their first game.
他们爱死我烤的香蕉面包了
And the guys love my banana bread.
闭上眼  在你睁开眼之前
Keep your eyes closed, and before you open them,
想想这20年来
remember that for 20 years,
你每年都给我完美的  贴心的礼物
you have given me perfect, creative, thoughtful gifts.
然而每年  我都让你失望
And every year, I have let you down.
你将会感到非常糟糕  我懂
You're about to feel really bad, and I know that,
因为这也是我每年的感受
because it's how I have felt every year.
但是亲爱的  这不是我的目的
But, honey, it is not my intention,
因为我爱你
because I love you.
结婚纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary.
天啊  中国杂技
Oh, my god. Chinese acrobats?!
20周年  中国[与"瓷器"同音]
20 years -- China.
你好聪明
You're brilliant.
-没错  -伙计们  你们是我的礼物
- You got it! - Hey, guys! You're my present!
那是什么
Oh -- oh, what's that?
直升机  直升机
那是直升机  我应该加入他们
That's the helicopter. I should get in there.
不不  让他们为你表演
No, no, they're -- they're here for you.
他们是来为你表演的
They're here for you.
亲爱的
Oh... honey.
别担心  只是两瓶啤酒
Don't worry, it was just a couple of beers,
而且你打扫干净了
and if you cleaned it up...
好的  海莉  我也爱你  拜拜
Okay, Haley, I love you, too. Bye.
抱歉  女士
Excuse me, ma'am.
听说你被通缉了
I hear you're a wanted woman.
你所见的可能对你不利[压在你身上]
What you see can and will be held against you.
那你得先抓到我
You're gonna have to arrest me first.
拿点酒来
Bring me some wine.
普先生  有件事我要向您坦白
Mr. P., I have a confession to make.
楼上有个更吸引人的"坦白"在等着我
I'm taking a much more interesting confession upstairs.
乔睡着后
After Joe went down,
我在泳池边喝了口小酒
I had a sip of beer by the pool,
结果瓶子碎了
and a bottle broke.
-是我干的  -别担心
- It was me. I did it. - Don't sweat it.
我也经常在照顾小孩之后喝啤酒
I popped a cold one after dealing with those kids --
有时候一边照顾一边喝
Sometimes during.
谢谢你  普先生  还有
Thanks, Mr. P. -- and, hey...
上去注意安全
Be careful up there.
我们还没那么熟
We are not that close.